export default chapter1 =()=>{
    return([
        {chapter:'Me and My Family',type:'DragAndDrop','title':' Drag and drop the correct answer',
    questions: [{question:'- is a carrot',options:["Green","Orange","Yellow","Purple","Red"],answer:'Orange'},
        {question:'- is the grass',options:["Green","Orange","Yellow","Purple","Red"],answer:'Green'},
        {question:'- is a bear',options:["Black","Red","Yellow","Brown","Blue"],answer:'Brown'},
        {question:'- is a plum',options:["Black","Blue","Yellow","Brown","Purple"],answer:'Purple'},
        {question:'- is a whale',options:["Black","Blue","Yellow","Brown","Purple"],answer:'Blue'},
        {question:'- is a witch’s hat',options:["Black","Orange","Yellow","Purple","Orange"],answer:'Black'}]   
     },
     {chapter:'Me and My Family',type:'SelectActivity','title':' Click on the correct answer',
    questions: [{question:'- is a carrot',options:["Green","Orange","Yellow","Purple","Red"],answer:'Orange'},
        {question:'- is the grass',options:["Green","Orange","Yellow","Purple","Red"],answer:'Green'},
        {question:'- is a bear',options:["Black","Red","Yellow","Brown","Blue"],answer:'Brown'},
        {question:'- is a plum',options:["Black","Blue","Yellow","Brown","Purple"],answer:'Purple'},
        {question:'- is a whale',options:["Black","Blue","Yellow","Brown","Purple"],answer:'Blue'},
        {question:'- is a witch’s hat',options:["Black","Orange","Yellow","Purple","Orange"],answer:'Black'}]   
     },
    ])
}